(Leonard (singing):)Hit on me, hit on me
(Leonard (singing):)Sorry Alex hit on me
I had no idea I'm cute
Aw. Damn it, you are.
(Leonard:)Please forgive me,
I should have told you about Alex.
(Penny:)I don't care about Alex. Fine, I care.
Okay, I hate the bitch.
(Penny:)But what really hurt
is that you liked it so much.
(Penny:)Do I need to be worried?
(Leonard:)Of course not. No. Why?
Because she's pretty and smart
and when you talk about work...
...she doesn't have to look up words
in the dictionary...
(Penny:)...to understand what you said.
(Leonard:)- You do that?
- No.
(Leonard:)Hang on. Are you feeling insecure?
Because that's my thing.
(Leonard:)And if you take it away, I don't know
what I'm bringing to this relationship.
(Penny:)Yes, Leonard, I am insecure. Happy?
(Leonard:)No, I'm not happy.